What the heck?
Why are you on my bed?
This is clearly my bed, okay?
This is really your room?
Rent overdue.
Bonus delayed.
A reckless brother, offending the boss.
And now I even have to take you in?
Why does every unlucky thing
happen to me?
From now on,
I'm your lucky star.
You, my lucky star?
That's all you're drinking?
Come on,
drink more.
Didn't expect you to have a decent figure.
Don't test my limits.
How much did I drink?
Wait a second!
No way, no way...
This is insane, insane, insane!
What kind of magic does this wine have?
It even made me, the almighty envoy, lose my memory.
What happened last night?
Nothing happened last night.
I'm warning you,
you can't tell anyone.
Nothing happened last night.
I actually established a connection.
With her?
This is too awkward.
Qi Miao!
Have some breakfast before you leave.
I won't eat.
I'm going to be late.
I need to go now.
Wait a second!
What's this?
A lunch I prepared for you.
Thank you.
I can't believe that I, a proud envoy of Blue Star,
actually established a connection on a foreign planet.
What should I do?
You're punctual.
President Qin.
I won't make the same mistake twice.
Alright.
Let's get started.
Mr. Qin.
This is the script I revised overnight.
You can take a look.
Okay.
I'm the one who revised it.
I won't back down this time.
Mr. Qin.
This is my previous version.
I made some adjustments.
How about I explain it directly?
Sure.
I like straightforwardness.
Go ahead.
Based on your habits during meetings,
I'll start with market trends, audience preferences,
and data analysis,
and explain my ideas step by step.
Regarding market trends,
I noticed a few extremely popular shows on the market.
I observed them closely.
Hello, bro.
Where are you?
Alright, I'll be right there.
Left alley is secure.
Confirmed.
Copy that.
Right alley is secure.
All clear.
Where's the item I asked for?
Hold on.
Careful, walls have ears. Got it?
You're overacting.
Where's my crystal?
Right here, bro.
Can't you show some respect for it?
Bro.
Isn't this being low-key?
Hand it over.
The energy crystal.
Finally, I...
Bro.
Then, the deposit...
I'll give it to you.
The rest...
I'll pay you after the exhibition.
Thank you, bro.
Ruichi bro!
What brings you here?
I've been looking for you everywhere.
Didn't expect you to walk right into me.
Bro...
You two know each other?
I'll deal with you later!
Do I have to arrest you myself...
Or will you come willingly?
Don't think for a second...
That you're still the high and mighty Bluecore Envoy.
Now the crystal's in my hands.
If someone's getting captured, it's gonna be you by me!
What's going on?
Oh my goodness!
What is going on here?
You think a little trick like that can fool me?
Chasing you all the way from Bluecore to Earth...
Why can't you just let me go?
You stole the forbidden fruit...
Breaking the laws of Bluecore.
You've hurt people maliciously.
The law demands punishment.
I just ate some stupid fruit!
Do you really have to go this far?
Hao Ruichi...
Can't you just let me stay here on Earth...
And live as an ordinary person?
If you hadn't fled from Bluecore...
Would I have faced all these troubles?
You can't run from the laws of Bluecore.
You've linked...
Never thought the esteemed Envoy...
Would form a bond...
With the opposite sex on another planet.
Hao Ruichi...
Just stay here with me obediently.
Enough nonsense!
Get back to Bluecore now!
I'd rather die...
Than return to that...
Cold and cruel Bluecore planet!
Just kill me.
Alright.
I'll take away your consciousness right now.
You're out of energy.
Hao Ruichi.
You can't go back either.
Stay here with me.
Even if I have to fight,
I'll knock you unconscious,
and carry you back.
Wait.
Hao Ruichi.
Did you forget?
Did you forget your lifelong agreement with Lan Kexing?
the promise you made?
If you leave,
what about your other half?
Hao Ruichi.
You've already obtained the most precious thing.
Why
do you still act like you don't care?
Hao Ruichi.
You're so cold-hearted.
A lofty emissary of Lan Kexing,
capable of seeing everyone's magnetic fields,
but unable to see through your own heart.
Hao Ruichi, oh Hao Ruichi,
you're truly pitiful.
I'm sorry, Brother Ruichi.
I really didn't know you weren't an Earthling.
If I had known,
I definitely wouldn't have been so reckless.
Is that the point?
I-I was wrong.
I swear I'll never steal from you again.
You're my only brother.
From now on, I'll listen to you alone.
I had my reasons for doing what I did.
Reasons?
What reasons?
I stole the crystals for my sister.
Your sister?